{
    "subject": "resource/Friedrich_von_Rabenau",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1884-10-10",
    "human_readable": "Friedrich von Rabenau was born on 1884-10-10.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9246188402175903,
            "question": "When was Friedrich von Rabenau born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8632465600967407,
            "question": "What is the birth date of Friedrich von Rabenau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8054737448692322,
            "question": "What year is associated with Friedrich von Rabenau's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7873426675796509,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthdate of Friedrich von Rabenau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7353574633598328,
            "question": "Who was born on October 10th, 1884?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6541315317153931,
            "question": "In what year did Friedrich von Rabenau begin his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6041961312294006,
            "question": "Who was born in 1884?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5855926275253296,
            "question": "Friedrich von Rabenau's birthdate falls in which month?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5798532962799072,
            "question": "On what date did Friedrich von Rabenau come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06001153215765953,
            "question": "October 10th holds significance for whom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Friedrich von Rabenau was born on 1884-10-10.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5776_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what date did Friedrich von Rabenau come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5776_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Friedrich von Rabenau's birthdate falls in which month?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5776_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was born in 1884?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5776_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5776_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention Friedrich von Rabenau's birthdate as 1884-10-10 (or similar variations, such as \"Born10.10.1884\")."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information across the documents supports that Friedrich von Rabenau was born on October 10, 1884."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}